Anywhere you are, distance is not a barrier.
Viewers you are called to battle against spiritual entities which cause crisis in your lives.
You and Prophet T.B Joshua together in the name of Jesus can stop satan killing, stealing and destroying
your life. Touch the screen right now.
Be engaged with God.
I want to pray with the viewers right now
Those who are under the influence of my voice
Whatever situation that you are in
I say be released in the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, whatever situation that you are in
it is not the will of God.
Be released in theme of Jesus!
It is the will of God to release you and I release you in the name of Jesus.
Listen, the voice of God says
"you are released in the name of Jesus!"
The voice of God say
Yes, I will not blame you that you are doubting.
Your doubt will not change anything.
Viewers, listen! You are doubting that
is it that I will be released?
I have suffered so much.
I say " You are released in the name of Jesus!"
Your doubt will not change anything.
Be released!
Whatever situation that it could be: hardship, setback, depression, affliction
I say "be released in the name of Jesus!"
I can see you being released.
A prophet says, "he can see you being released."
Viewers what does that mean to you?
I want to hear from you, what does this mean to you?
What does it mean to you?
If you honor a prophet because he is a prophet of God
you will receive his reward.
If a prophet says right now, you are released!
What does it mean to you?
You are delivered! What does it mean to you?
You are healed! What does it mean to you?
You are free! What does it mean to you?
You are saved! What does it mean to you?
In Jesus name!
Yes!
That is the confession that God wants to hear.
That when a prophet says you are released, what does it mean to you?
You say, "you are released." That is all.
From your mouth, faith comes.
Yes, yes, faith comes
No, no comes doubt.
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God as you send your testimony
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you just have watched
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophesies, deliverances, service and testimonies.
From the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing the nations, and changing the world